USHA NEPAL —

https://www.linkedin.com/in/usha-nepal-984637302/

Tikathali, Lalitpur, Nepal | +977-9863947610 | ushanepal778@gmail.com

SUMMARY:

I'm keen to enhance my working capacities and professional skills and to serve the organization best with sheer determination and commitment with expertise in problem-solving skills, dedicated to personal as well as corporate growth and improvements.

TECHNICAL SKILLS & ABILITIES:

- Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word)
- Project Management, Event Management, Product and Service knowledge
- Financial knowledge and analysis
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM) Software, Customer Retention
- · Contract and document management, Public Relation
- Content Writing, Good communication
- Interactive, Team player, Ability to adopt new environment

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Softechpark Pvt. Ltd.

Project Manager | March, 2024 - Present

 Working as a Project Manager at softechpark, I excel at managing projects with Trello, fostering client relationships, and utilizing financial analysis. Skilled in CRM software, contracts, and content creation, I thrive in collaborative environments and adapt quickly to new situations.

Daraz Kaymu Pvt. Ltd

Customer Service Representative (CSC Voice) | July 2023 - February 2024

• As a customer support at Daraz Kyamu Pvt. Ltd. resolving inquiries and fostering client satisfaction. This experience honed my communication and problem-solving skills.

ECA, PARTICIPATION, COURSES & CERTIFICATION:

- Troop leader of Heritage scout troop at Scout Nepal
- Vice President at Interact Club of Goldengate
- Advisor at Nawasrijana Club
- · General Member at Rotaract Club of Balaju
- · Joint Secretary at Leo Club of Kathmandu Imperial

EDUCATION:

2023 - Present | Nepal Commerce Campus | Tribhuwan University

Bachelor in Business Administration (BBA-Finance)

2021 | Golden Gate International College | National Education Board

10+2 Physics | Science

REFERENCE:

Yunesh Khadgi | Customer Care Manager - Voice

Daraz Kyamu Pvt. Ltd.

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuneshkhadgi/

Bhagwan Das Agrahari | Founder & CEO

Softechpark Pvt. Ltd.

https://np.linkedin.com/in/bhagwan-das-agrahari-089bb818a